MATEJ JURIN

matejjurin278@gmail.com

https://github.com/Matej404

07547381355, Earl's Court, London

Work permit holder, I do not need sponsorship

Objective

I am extremely interested in the branch of Web Development, and I have a great desire to upgrade my knowledge about it. I am planning to work as Front-End Web Developer and consider your company a great opportunity where I could learn a lot. I would be happy to get the opportunity for further education and gaining work experience that would push me in a full-stack direction.

Skills

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript
- Experienced with front-end frameworks such as React.js
- Experienced with SQL and Node.js
- Experienced with PHP
- Strong knowledge of responsive design and mobile-first development
- Familiar with version controls systems, knowledge of using GIT
- Understanding of cross-browser compatibility and web accessibility standards
- Knowledge of UI/UX principles and best practices
- Ability to work collaboratively in a team environment
- Excellent problem-solving and debugging skills
- Strong attention to detail and commitment to delivering high-quality work

Education

2022 – 2024 FULL-STACK DEVELOPMENT

IT Switch Career, London, UK

Projects

PORTFOLIO - https://matejjurin.co.uk/portfolio/portfolio/

GAZETTEER - https://matejjurin.co.uk/project1/project1/

COMPANY DIRECTORY - https://matejjurin.co.uk/project2/project2/

Working Experience

2023 – Present Concierge/Receptionist

Property Managment Recruitment, London, UK

2019-2023 Gym Instructor/Personal Trainer LB44 FITNESS, London, UK

2011 – 2018 Kickboxing and MMA Fighter/Trainer Leon Gym, Zagreb, Croatia

Personal Interest

Various sports, live music, reading